One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Mink Pedro, Captain of the Guardians
قائد حراس المينك بيدرو
My leg...
...قدماي
Damn! I can't move!
سحقًا، لا أستطيع التحرك
Chopper-san !
تشوبر-سان
Brook!
بروك
You fools...
أيها الأحمقان، ستتغلغل هذه الحلوى داخل جسدكما ببطء
It's no use. You won't be able to move anymore.
لا فائدة، ستعجزان عن التحرك من مكانكما
Chopper-san !
تشوبر-سان
Don't panic, don't panic.
لا تخافا، لا تخافا
Goodness...
...بحقكما
What made you think you'd be able to take your ship back?
ما الذي دفعكما للاعتقاد بأنّكما قادران على استعادة السفينة؟
In order to catch you guys,
بهدف القبض عليكم
we've mobilized all of our soldiers across the island
إننا نحشد جميع جنودنا في أنحاء الجزيرة لفرض شبكة حصار منيعة
You cannot escape from us.
لا مفر لكم في أي مكان
The difference in our power is clear!
فارق القوة واضح للعيان
Damn!
سحقًا
I... I can't even transform!
لـ-لا أستطيع التحول حتّى
Let Chopper-san go!
حرّر تشوبر-سان
Idiot! It's too late!
فات الأوان أيها الأحمق
This is your punishment for defying me.
هذه عقوبة الوقوف في وجهي
I'll turn you into a candy man and lick you until you're gone.
سأحولكما إلى رجلي حلوى ثم ألعقكما-بيرورين
The candy will coat your whole body,
ستُغطي الحلوى جسدكما بأكمله
and fill up your entire body until you can't breathe anymore.
وستتغلغل وتقطع نفسكما
And with that agony...
...وبهذا العذاب
it will take only three minutes to kill you!
سيستغرق الأمر ثلاث دقائق لقتل الهدف
No way...
مُحال
And then, it will be complete! A sweet candy man!
وبعدها ستصبح جثة رجل الحلوى الحلوة جاهزة
Chopper-san !
تشوبر-سان
Stop!
توقف
It's too late to regret your choices!
فات الأوان للندم على قراركما
Remember... I gave you a chance!
منحتكما فرصة بالفعل
I offered to let the two of you go.
قلتُ أنني سأدعكما ترحلان أنتما الاثنان فقط
You guys are clueless!
لكنكما قللتما من شأننا
This island...
...هذه الجزيرة
isn't sweet at all!
ليست حلوة على الإطلاق
Chopper-san !
تشوبر-سان
Why don't you sit back and count the seconds?
فلتبقى هادئًا وتعد الثواني
This is exactly what sweet fools such as yourselves deserve...
هذا ما يستحقه أحمقان مثلكما
Oh, stop! I don't wanna get sweetened!
توقف، لا أريد التحول إلى حلوى
Oh, stop!
توقف
I'll turn you into a candy man and lick you!
سأحولك إلى رجل حلوى وألعقك
Hey, Big Brother Peros!
يا أخي بيروس
That's Mama...
إنّها ماما
Wedding...
...كعكة
She's still on her ravenous rampage...
لن تتوقف نوبة جوعها
...cake!
الزفاف
We need to lure her to Cacao Island where Pudding is waiting.
علينا إرشادها إلى جزيرة الكاكاو حيث بودينغ
If she finds out there's no cake on this ship, she'll kill me.
إن اكتشفت عدم وجود كعكة على هذه السفينة، فسوف تقتلني
I don't think we're at that stage yet.
لا أظننا وصلنا إلى تلك المرحلة بعد
Let me eat!
...دعوني أتناول
Cake!
الكعكة
It's the coast! Get to the Sunny !
إنّه الساحل، أسرعوا بركوب سفينة الساني
He's still alive? Straw Hat...
قبعة القش على قيد الحياة؟
Our soldiers must've been the ones wiped out by the lightning...
لا بدّ أنّ جنودنا من تعرضوا للصاعقة
Who are those guys?!
من هؤلاء؟
They've hijacked the ship!
لقد استولوا على السفينة
What? Brook?! Chopper?!
ماذا؟ بروك؟ تشوبر؟
What's that?!
ما ذلك؟
Get back to the Mirro-world.
عودوا إلى عالم المرايا
If you stay,
...سينتهي المطاف بجميعكم
you'll be lying at his feet in a few seconds.
جاثمين تحت قدميه في غضون ثواني
Jump into the mirror!
أسرعوا بدخول المرآة
Perospero and Katakuri... Those two of all others...
...بيروسبيرو وكاتاكوري من بين الجميع
The disaster continues!
ما زلنا في مأزق عويص
It's amazing that you got this far... I'm impressed.
أبليتم حسنًا ببلوغ هذه المسافة، أثرتم إعجابي
But you're going to a graveyard now!
ولكن وجهتكم هي مقبرتكم
This is where you all must die!
ستهلكون هنا
Candy Maiden!
حلوى العذراء كاندي مايدين
A wall of candy!
جدار من الحلوى
It's obvious that it's not just a wall!
من الواضح أنّه ليس مجرّد جدار
Fishman Karate...
كاراتيه البرمائيين غيوجين كاراتيه
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Shark Tile Fist!
لكمة قرميد القرش ساميغاوارا سيكن
Jet Bazooka!
البازوكا النفاث جيت بازوكا
Yes!
مرحى
Not yet, not yet...
ليس بعد
Don't underestimate me!
لا تستهينوا بي
Huh? What is it?!
ما هذا؟
Candy Maiden...
كاندي مايدين
Decoration!
الزخرفة ديكورشيون
It's gigantic...
يا لضخامته
This is the end!
حانت نهايتكم
No one can get through here!
لا أحد سيصل إلى هنا
Go around and get to the ship!
التفوا من حوله لصعود السفينة
No, run straight!
كلا، اركضوا نحو الأمام
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Red Hawk!
الصقر الأحمر ريد هوك
Is that a flame?!
لهب؟
His powers are just like Luffy's!
قدرته مشابهة لقدرة لوفي
Wedding...
...كعكة
cake!
الزفاف
Here she comes!
إنّها قادمة
What should we do, Luffy?! We're surrounded!
ما العمل يا لوفي؟ نحن محاصرون
Luffy! Force Katakuri off the ship!
لوفي، اقذف كاتاكوري بعيدًا عن السفينة
We'll find a way to set sail!
سنحاول الإبحار بطريقة ما
I got it!
دع هذا لي
– This way! – Okay!
من هذا الاتجاه
That bastard! He must've come from the mirror dimension!
ذلك اللعين، لا بدّ أنّه جاء بواسطة عالم المرآيا
Wedding cake!
كعكة الزفاف
I don't want to be in the path of Mama's ravenous rampage.
لا أود التورط في نوبة جوع ماما-بيرورين
Armament: Hardening!
هاكي التسلح بوسو كوكا
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Hawk Gatling!
رشاش الصقر هوك غاتلينغ
Why?! I'm using haki, but I can't hit him!
...لماذا؟ إنّه لا يتأثر حتّى باستخدام الهاكي
Chopper! Brook! Are you all right?!
تشوبر، بروك، هل أنتما بخير؟
Stay with us!
تماسكا
Where is it?
...أين هي
The cake!
الكعكة؟
Carrot.
كاروت
Try not to be startled by this sudden turn of events.
لا تتفاجئي مما سيحدث
What?
ماذا؟
I have a suspicion...
...أعتقد
that Luffy and his crew...
...أنّ لوفي وطاقمه
The ones who will guide us to the new dawn!
إنّهم الأشخاص الذين سيقودون العالم إلى فجرٍ جديد
For centuries?!
منذ قرون؟
Hey, Mont d'Or, can you hear me?
يا مونت دور، أتسمعني؟
Yeah, I can hear you.
أجل، أسمعك
Surround Whole Cake Island's southwestern coast with battleships.
حاصر ساحل الجنوبي الغربي لجزيرة الكعكة الكاملة بالسفن الحربية حالًا
Right away, Brother Peros!
عُلم يا أخي بيروس
I guess Straw Hat and the others are still alive.
يبدو أنّ قبعة القش والآخرين ما زالوا على قيد الحياة
A Coup de...
...كودو
What?!
ماذا؟
Coup de Burst! This ship is capable of flying a kilometer away!
الكودو باست، بوسع هذه السفينة الطيران للأمام بمسافة كيلو متر
If we try to just set sail, Big Mom will sink us in no time!
إن أبحرنا بشكل عادي، فستُغرق بيغ مام السفينة
I don't really understand, but this is the best way to escape, right?
لم أفهم الأمر تمامًا، لكنك تعنين أنّه بوسعنا الهرب؟
Yeah!
أجل
Okay! Then let's bet on it!
عظيم، لنراهن على ذلك
Big Mom is coming!
بيغ مام قادمة
There you are!
وجدتكم
Carrot! You go help them get ready to set sail!
كاروت، اذهبي لمساعدتهم على الإبحار
What?
ماذا؟
Hurry up!
أسرعي
Okay!
أجل
Is it there?
أهي هناك؟
The wedding cake?!
كعكة الزفاف؟
Hey, Brook, Chopper! Stay with me!
يا بروك، تشوبر، تماسكا لبعض الوقت
Even if we make it out of here, it'll be meaningless if you two die!
لا فائدة ترجى من خروجنا إن هلكتما
We spotted the Straw Hats at the southwest coast!
رصدنا طاقم قبعة القش في ساحل الجنوب غربي
This is Minister Amande aboard the Nuts Island tarte.
معك الوزيرة أماند من قوّات جزيرة تارت
We'll corner Straw Hat and the others.
سنحاصر قبعة القش والآخرين
This is terrible.
هذا لا يبشر بخير، سُفنهم الحربية قادمة من البحر، وبيغ مام من اليابسة
We're completely trapped in the middle!
نحن محاصرون تمامًا
Nami! We have to set sail!
نامي، علينا الإسراع وإلا وقعنا في مشكلة
I know! But I have to load two more barrels of cola!
أعلم، لكن ما زال عليّ تعبئة برميلان من الكولا
I'll load the rest. You go prepare for the Coup-de-whatever!
سأتولى الباقي، لذا اذهبي أنتِ وجهزي الكودو أو أيًّا كان اسمها
All right, I'll leave it to you, then!
حسنًا، أعتمد عليكِ
Candy Wave!
موجة الحلوى كاندي ويف
What?!
ماذا؟
Candy?!
حلوى؟
Oh no! There's no way we can use the Coup de Burst like this!
ما العمل؟ لن نستطيع استخدام الكودو باست هكذا
What's wrong?!
ما الخطب؟
This is bad! The Sunny has been trapped by candy!
هذه مصيبة، علقت السفينة بالحلوى
What?!
ماذا؟
Did you see the power of my Candy Wave?!
هل رأيتم مدى قوة موجة الحلوى؟
I'm a perfectionist!
أنا أحبّ المثالية
Oh, there he is!
إنّه هناك
What should we do?
ما الذي علينا فعله؟
Turn Brook and Chopper back, as well as the ship, candy jerk!
أعد بروك وتشوبر إلى طبيعتهما، وكذلك السفينة يا أحمق الحلوى
If nothing is done...
...على هذا المعدل
Cake!
كعكة
You'll either be destroyed by Mama
إما تسحقكم ماما أولًا
or destroyed by our cannons!
أو تُغرقكم قصف المدافع
Either way, your chance of survival is zero!
بكلتا الحالتين، لا تملكون أدنى فرصة للنجاة
Beast Sword: Imperial Guardian Lion!
سيف الوحش: الأسد الحارس جيوكين كاراجيشي
Hey, do you know what my bounty is?
أنت، أتعرف ما مقدار المكافأة على رأسي؟
It's 700 million.
إنّها 700 مليون
A weakling like you has no chance of defeating me.
هيهات أن أُهزم أمام ضعيف مثلك
You escaped death. Lick.
لقد نجوت من الموت-بيرورين
It's pointless to die here! The day of the new dawn is coming!
لا فائدة من الموت هنا، ففجر العالم قد اقترب
I must go back to my country!
يجب أن أعود إلى موطني
You're so handsome.
أنت وسيم للغاية
I'll reduce it to 50 years.
سأجعلها 50 سنة
Go on with your life.
امضِ في حياتك
At that time,
آنذاك
if you hadn't sacrificed your left eye, you would've been killed for sure...
لو أنّك لم تضحي بعينك اليسرى، كنتَ لتقتل لا محالة
Did you want to survive that badly?
هل أردت النجاة لتلك الدرجة؟
All right...
على أيّ حال، كم عمرك الآن؟
I'm 27...
27 سنة
So 50 years of your life were drained away, meaning it's more like you've lived 77 years.
سُلبت 50 سنة من عمرك، لذا يصبح مجموع ما عشته هو 77 سنة
Now, I wonder how many years you expect to live...
والآن، كم تبقّى من عمرك يا تُرى؟
At the very least, I'd like to choose where I die.
على الأقل سأحدد مكان موتي بنفسي
By the way,
بالمناسبة، بما أنّك كنتَ قائد ... طاقم قراصنة نوكس
"Nox" means "night," right?
فهل «نوكس» تعني الليل؟
That sounds pretty negative.
إنّه اسم سلبي نوعًا ما
They say, "Every night comes to an end."
لكل ليلة نهاية كما يقال
And...
...مما يعني
"nox" is the same as...
أنّ نوكس تحمل المعنى ذاته
"just before dawn."
وهو الليل الذي يسبق الفجر
If I can serve as the foundation for
إن أمكنني المساعدة في تمهيد بزوغ فجر العالم الذي يترقبه سيدي والآخرين
then I'll have accomplished what I want most.
فهذا كل ما أريده
I think I have enough time for that...
أظنني أملك الوقت الكافي لفعل ذلك
You once said that "just before the dawn" and "nox" meant the same thing...
ذات مرة قلتَ أنّ الليل الذي يسبق الفجر و«نوكس» تشيران إلى المعنى ذاته
But the only thing that's waiting for you is the eternal darkness known as death.
لكن كل ما ينتظرك هو ظلام أبدي يُدعى الموت
No...
...كلا
Roger! Lord Oden! I'm beggin' you, take me along!
روجر، أودين-ساما، خذاني معكما
I'll do anything! Take me with you!
سأفعل أي شيء، لذا خذاني معكما
Kid, you still have to wait.
أيها الطفل، ما تزال غير مستعدًّا
I'm not a kid, I'm Pedro!
لستُ طفلًا، أنا بيدرو
My time is limited.
لم يتبقى لي الكثير من الوقت
Listen! Everyone gets their own turn.
اسمع، سيحين دور كل شخص عاجلًا أم آجلًا
Be patient and wait!
تحلى بالصبر وانتظر
It'll come naturally. Your turn, I mean...
فدورك سيحين يومًا ما بكل تأكيد
Goodbye, Pedro.
إلى اللقاء يا بيدرو
I understand, Roger!
فهمت يا روجر
Pedro!
بيدرو
Roger...
...روجر قد
What about Roger?
ما به روجر؟
They're saying he died!
مات
Roger said, "Everyone gets their own turn"!
قال روجر: سيحين دور كل شخص عاجلًا أم آجلًا
What are you talking about?
عمّ تتحدث؟
This is my turn!
وقد حان دوري الآن
This will break all of your magic spells, right?
هذا سيمحو كل تعاويذك السحرية، أليس كذلك؟
Bombs?!
قنابل؟
Stop, you fool! What do you think you're doing?!
توقف أيها اللعين، بمَ تفكر؟
Let go of me!
أفلتني
I...
...أنا
Huh?
ماذا؟
had a feeling that this would be my last journey.
ينتابني شعور أنّ هذه ستكون رحلتي الأخيرة
What do you mean, Pedro?
ماذا تعني يا بيدرو؟
Pedro?!
بيدرو؟
Farewell.
الوداع
What do you mean, Pedro?
ماذا تعني يا بيدرو؟
One day, you'll see how important it was...
يومًا ما، ستدركين مدى أهمية إنقاذ لوفي وطاقمه هنا ومساعدتهم على الإبحار
Pedro!
بيدرو
Listen!
اسمعوا
You-gara must press on!
عليكم المضي قدمًا
Pedro!
بيدرو
Don't tell me Big Bro Peros is...
...أيعقل أنّ أخي بيروس
were caught in the explosion!
علقا في الانفجار
That candy he produced is starting to melt!
بدأت حلوى قدرته بالذوبان
I can't believe he sacrificed himself...
لا أصدق أنّه ضحى بنفسه
How could you do that, Pedro!
ما الذي فعلته يا بيدرو؟
I thought I was done for!
ظننت أنني سأموت
Are you guys all right?!
هل أنتما بخير؟
Stop, Carrot!
كلا يا كاروت
Let go of me! Let me go back to where Pedro was! Maybe he's still alive!
دعيني، عليّ الذهاب لمكان بيدرو، ربما ما يزال حيًّا
No! You saw that explosion... He saved us!
كلا، لقد أنقذنا عبر ذلك الانفجار
We had no chance to survive until now!
كان أملنا في النجاة معدومًا حتّى تلك اللحظة
You have to understand why Pedro did what he did! Please!
أرجو أن تتفهمي دافع بيدرو
Ready to fly, Nami?!
هل نحن مستعدون للتحليق يا نامي؟
Yes, it's all set!
نحن على أهبة الاستعداد
Chopper! Brook! Are you with us?
تشوبر، بروك، أأنتما على ما يُرام؟
Oh?
ماذا؟
Jinbe!
جينبي؟
Yes, they're with us!
أجل، إنّهما على ما يُرام
Set sail, you guys!
لنُبحر يا رفاق
If we waste this moment,
...إن أهدرنا هذه اللحظة
then Pedro would be ashamed of us!
ستذهب تضحية بيدرو هباءً
We'll escape from here no matter what!
سنخرج من هنا بكل تأكيد
At any cost!
مهما كلّف الثمن
Why is everyone...
...لِمَ جميعكم
so heated up?
أصابتكم العاطفة؟
Get out of here, Big Mom Pirates!
ارحلوا يا قراصنة بيغ مام
Carrot!
كاروت
Oops...
...مؤلم
Get up! Get on your feet, Carrot! And take the sword!
انهضي، قفي على أقدامكِ والتقطي السيف يا كاروت
She has no aptitude for swords.
إنّها ليست مناسبة للسيوف
Pedro! This is none of your business!
بيدرو، هذا ليس من شأنك
Carrot will become a strong swordswoman under my guidance.
ستغدو كاروت مبارزة قوية تحت إشرافي
What is this?
ما هذا؟
Take a fighting pose.
جربيها
That suits you much better.
هذا يناسبك أكثر
You are capable of floating in the air for a while.
يمكنكِ الطفو في الهواء لفترة طويلة
If you take advantage of that and Electro, you can acquire your own strength and way of fighting.
إن استغليتِ هذه الأفضلية مع الإيلكترو فيمكنكِ اكتساب القوة وأسلوبك الشخصي في القتال
Are you sure?
حقًّا؟
Yes.
أجل
Come at me! I'll be your training partner.
هاجميني، سأكون شريككِ في التدريب
All right!
عظيم
I thought I couldn't become strong.
ظننتُ أنني لن أصبح قوية
I can't believe there's a skill suited for me.
لم أتخيل وجود أسلوب يناسبني
It's all thanks to you, Pedro.
هذا بفضلك يا بيدرو
It doesn't matter how you fight.
أسلوب قتالك ليس مهمًّا
From now on, you must be a strong fighter and be constantly prepared.
من الآن فصاعدًا عليكِ أن تصبحي محاربة قوية وتكوني مستعدة دائمًا
Everyone gets their own turn.
سيحين دور كل شخص عاجلًا آم آجلًا
Don't worry...
لا تقلقي
Electrical...
الكهربة إيلكتريك
As long as I'm here, you will not set sail!
ما دمتُ موجودًا، فلن أسمح لكم بالإبحار
Get away from Carrot!
ابتعد عن كاروت
Carrot! Leave him to me!
كاروت، دعي أمره لي
Luffy...
لوفي
I hope you're strong enough to force me out...
آمل أنّك قوي بما يكفي لطردي خارج السفينة
We'll set sail! I'm the captain of this ship!
سنبحر حتمًا، فأنا قبطان هذه السفينة
Gum-Gum Elephant Gun!
غومو غومو نو
The sails can stay like that.
لندع الأشرعة على حالها
Toward the northwest, Coup de Burst!
نحو الشمال غربي بالكودو باست
Azimuth: 45 degrees to the northwest!
الزاوية: 45 درجة نحو الشمال غربي
I see...
فهمت
I certainly can't attack the others if you do that.
بالفعل، لن أستطيع مهاجمة الآخرين إن فعلت ذلك
This way, you can't stop it even if you know what'll happen!
بهذه الطريقة لن تستطيع فعل شيء حتّى بمعرفتك بما سيحدث
Brother! I'm here to save you!
أخي، لقد أتيت لإنقاذك
We'll avenge Big Bro Peros!
سأنتقم لأخي بيروس
All ships, prepare to fire toward the enemy ship!
على جميع السفن الاستعداد لإطلاق النار تجاه سفينة العدو
Adjust the cannon's shot!
اضبطوا زاوية الارتفاع
Shark-chan, come back!
عُد أيها القرش
Chopper-san, can you grab it on that side? Let's pull it close to the Sunny before they start shooting!
تشوبر-سان، تعال إلى هنا لنسحبها قريبًا من السفينة قبل أن يشنّوا هجومهم
Carrot! Hang on. Can you get up?
كاروت، تماسكي، أيمكنكِ النهوض؟
Yes... Nami, thank you.
أجل، نامي، شكرًا لكِ
Where is it?!
أين هي؟
Big Mom!
بيغ مام؟
We're really in trouble now! We have to escape before the ship is destroyed!
هذه مصيبة، علينا الخروج من هنا بسرعة قبل أن تتحطم السفينة
Is that... Pedro?! Is he alive?!
أذلك بيدرو؟ أهو حي؟
Damn! Pedro, that bastard!
سحقًا لك يا بيدرو اللعين
That's not Pedro!
إنّه ليس بيدرو
No...
مُحال
Oh, man... I felt my blood going cold...
سحقًا، شعرتُ بتجمد دمي
My Candy Armor was completely destroyed!
...لقد دُمّر درع الحلوى خاصتي تمامًا
No way... Why is he alive?!
مُحال، لِمَ هو على قيد الحياة؟
It looks like all of the second round shots were intercepted!
أُعترضت جميع قذائف الجولة الثانية
Third round! Hurry up and load!
الجولة الثالثة، أسرعوا بشحن الذخيرة
L-Let go of me!
أ-أفلتني
Nami! Carrot!
نامي، كاروت
Jinbe!
جينبي
Brook!
بروك
Chopper!
تشوبر
Listen to me!
استمعوا إلي
I'll be back! I'll leave the rest to you!
سأعود حتمًا، سأترك الباقي لكم
What?! What do you mean by that?!
ماذا؟ ماذا تعني بذلك؟
When the lever returns to its original position, the burst is ready!
عندما يعود المقبض إلى موضعه الأصلي، فإنّ التعبئة اكتملت
All right, everyone! Hang onto something!
حسنًا جميعًا، تشبثوا بشيءٍ ما
I got it!
فهمت
We're ready anytime!
نحن مستعدون بأي لحظة
We're ready too!
نحن مستعدتان أيضًا
Okay, here we go!
عظيم، هيا بنا
Don't let the Straw Hats get away! Fire!
لا تسمحوا لقبعة القش والآخرين بالهرب، أطلقوا
Now!
الآن
Everybody! Don't forget to shout it!
لا تنسوا الصراخ يا رفاق
Coup de...
كودو
Burst!
باست
This is Amande.
معك أماند
The enemy ship flew into the sky.
هربت سفينة العدو... عبر السماء
The sky?!
عبر السماء؟
Hey, where's Luffy?!
أين لوفي؟
That's Straw Hat!
إنّه قبعة القش
Run!
اهربوا
Mirro-world
عالم المرايا
You succeeded...
أحسنت بفعلها
Here, I can beat you up as much as I want!
يمكنني قتالك بكل ما أوتيت من قوّة هنا
The path to the ship!
...الطريق إلى السفينة
He destroyed it himself!
قطعه على نفسه
So this is your determination as captain...
إذًا هذا قرار القبطان؟
But... you are no match for me.
لكنك لست ندًّا لي
This is where you will die.
سيكون هذا المكان قبرك
I'll return to the Sunny...
سأعود إلى سفينة الساني
as soon as I take you down!
بعد أن أهزمك